### Privacy Policy insuranceratesforless.com

Last Updated October 1, 2023

This privacy policy applies to the information you may provide to us when you visit [insuranceratesforless.com](https://auto.insuranceratesforless.com/) (the “**Website**”, “**Site**”). Please read this policy carefully to understand our information practices regarding the specific service you request.

By using this Website or any of the services offered on or through the Website, you are agreeing that you have read, understand, and accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

We will collect and use personal information about you that you enter on our Website to respond to your request for products and services offered through this Site. We do not collect any personally identifiable information from you unless you voluntarily choose to disclose such information while taking advantage of the services available on this Site. When completing the form on our Website, you may be asked to enter personal information such as your first and last name, street address, email address, phone number, etc. We also may collect general information such as your gender, age, birth date, zipcode, etc. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

When you use the Website for any service we offer, we may also collect non-personally identifiable data about your activity when visiting the Website, including the pages you view, your preference settings, the IP address assigned to the computer you use when visiting the Website, the type of browser you use, your operating system, and whether you reached our website directly or by clicking on a link. This data is not personally identifiable. It helps us determine the extent to which our visitors use certain parts of the Website, which, in turn, enables us to make the Website as useful as possible.

We also track the number of visitors to our Website that come from one of our promotional partners’ websites and the identity of the promotional partner that directed the individual to our Website. We record this information to determine if our online marketing or promotional campaigns are successful.

Additionally, we record your Internet Protocol (IP) addresses when you visit our Website. An IP Address is a number that is used by other computers to identify your computer when you log on to the Internet.

To assist us in providing services on the Website, we use third party vendors, who use various technologies, including scripts and cookies, to conduct tracking, analytics, and related services, including Lead Intelligence, Inc. d/b/a Jornaya, whose privacy policy you can view here: [https://www.jornaya.com/consumer-privacy-policy](https://www.jornaya.com/consumer-privacy-policy), and Active Prospect, Inc. d/b/a Trusted Form.

We use these vendors’ technologies and the information collected to administer the Website, analyze trends, measure ad performance, track users’ movements around the site (including the capture of visual snapshots of your activity on our site), and gather demographic information about our user base. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

### Do We Use Cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that can be transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser. Cookies enable us to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information that you previously shared with us, such as your setting preferences. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, to keep track of advertisements, to track visitors through our Website, and to compile data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer a better experience in the future. If you prefer, you can choose to have your browser notify you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies altogether. If you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.

### How Do We Use Your Information?

We may use your personally identifiable information to provide you our services, including when you request to be connected with insurance providers. We do this by sharing your information with third parties so they may correspond with you and provide you with information that you have requested. Please be advised that insuranceratesforless.com is not an insurance company or provider.

We may use your non-personal information to personalize and improve your experience on our Website; to respond to your communications with us; to improve our customer service; for internal research, recordkeeping, and reporting purposes; and for our own marketing purposes.

### How Do We Share Your Information?

We may share information that we collect with our vendors or service providers who help us operate our business; for our own marketing purposes; for our affiliates’, service providers’, and other third parties’ marketing purposes; in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; when we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company, our employees, our Website users, or others; or to enforce our Website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies. We may also transfer any data we collect in connection with a corporate change such as a merger, our acquisition by another company, or a partial or total sale of our assets (including as part of a bankruptcy proceeding).

### Third Party Websites

This Website may contain links or references to third party websites. This privacy policy does not cover any personally identifiable information that you provide to the owner of a third party website. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the “privacy policy” link typically located at the bottom of the web page you are visiting.

### Interest Based Advertising

We may partner with ad networks and other ad serving providers (“Advertising Providers”) who serve ads on behalf of us and others on non-affiliated sites. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information Advertising Providers collect about your visits to this site and elsewhere over time.

You may visit www.aboutads.info to learn more about this type of advertising and how to opt-out of this form of advertising by companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) self-regulatory program. Note that electing to opt out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. In addition, note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice. Opting-Out of Email Communications

You may choose to register to receive email communications from us directly on our website or through a third party. Upon registering, we will periodically send you newsletters and other e-mails featuring special and exclusive offers, promotions and other members-only benefits. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by sending an email to compliance@insuranceratesforless.com. You may also opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. We take reasonable administrative, physical, and technical measures to maintain the data that we collect in a secure fashion.

### USE OF SITE BY MINORS

The Site is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Site.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, add, or delete provisions of this privacy policy at any time. We will post the effective date of the most recent change at the top of this privacy policy. We urge you to come back to this Website and review this privacy policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you when you use this Website.

### Nevada Privacy Rights

Under Nevada law, Nevada residents may submit a request directing us not to make certain disclosures of personal information we maintain about them.

To exercise this right, please contact us:

* By email at compliance@insuranceratesforless.com

### Privacy Policy for California Residents

Print this page

This section contains disclosures required by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and applies only to “personal information” that is subject to the CCPA. Consumers with disabilities may access this notice by calling us at (888) 390-0192.

**Personal Information We Collect, Disclose for a Business Purpose, Sell and Share.** We collect the categories of personal information about California consumers identified in the chart below. As further set forth in the chart below, in the past 12 months, we have disclosed and sold California consumers’ personal information to third parties for business or commercial purposes.

| Categories of Personal Information | Collected in the last 12 months: | Categories of sources from which information is collected: | Business and commercial purposes for collecting, using, selling, and sharing: | Disclosed for business purposes to the following categories of third parties in the last 12 months: | Sold to and shared with the following categories of third parties in the last 12 months: |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Personal and online identifiers (such as first and last name, email address, or unique online identifiers) | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Categories of information described in Section 1798.80(e) of the California Civil Code (such as physical characteristics or description, insurance policy number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information) | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (such as race or gender) | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Commercial or transactions information (such as records of personal property or products or services purchased, obtained or considered) | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity information (such as browsing history, search history, interactions with a website, email, application, or advertisement) | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Geolocation Data | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Professional or employment-related information | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Education information | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Inferences drawn from the above information about your predicted characteristics and preferences | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |
| Other information about you that is linked to the personal information above | Yes | All categories of sources listed below. | All purposes listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. | All categories of third parties listed below. |

**Categories of Sources** We collect this personal information from the following categories of sources:

* Consumers;
* Service providers;
* Affiliates not under the InsuranceRatesForLess brand
* Consumer data resellers

**Business and Commercial Purposes for Collecting, Using, Selling, and Sharing California Personal Information.** We collect, use, sell, and share the personal information we collect for our commercial and business purposes, as further described in this Privacy Policy. These purposes include, without limitation:

* Our commercial purposes, including marketing, advertising, and enabling and promoting commercial transactions.
* Our business purposes as identified in the CCPA, which include:

* Auditing related to our interactions with you;
* Legal compliance;
* Detecting and protecting against security incidents, fraud, and illegal activity;
* Debugging;
* Performing services (for us or our service provider) such as account servicing, processing orders and payments, and analytics;
* Internal research for technological improvement;
* Internal operations;
* Activities to maintain and improve our services; and
* Other one-time uses

### Third Parties Who Receive California Personal Information.

We disclosed within the last 12 months, and currently disclose, the categories of personal information designated above to the categories of third parties listed below for business purposes:

* Service providers;
* Affiliates not under the InsuranceRatesForLess brand;
* Advertising networks;
* Internet service providers;
* Data analytics providers;
* Operating systems and platforms;
* Social networks; and
* Consumer data resellers

We sold within the last 12 months, and currently sell, the categories of personal information designated above to the categories of third parties listed below:

* Advertising/marketing companies;
* Advertising networks;
* Internet service providers;
* Automotive companies;
* Business services/agencies;
* Business to business companies;
* Communication services companies;
* Marketing data companies;
* Data analytics providers;
* Operating systems and platforms;
* Social networks;
* Consumer data resellers;
* Educational institutions & companies;
* Financial services companies;
* Home and automobile insurance companies;
* Lifestyle & interest product companies;
* Not-for-profit organizations;
* Publishing product companies;
* Technology/computer software companies;
* Telecommunications companies;
* Affiliates not under the InsuranceRatesForLess brand

**Your Rights Regarding Personal Information.** California residents have certain rights with respect to the personal information collected by businesses. If you are a California resident, you may exercise the following rights regarding your personal information, subject to certain exceptions and limitations:

* The right to know the categories and specific pieces of personal information we collect, use, disclose, and sell about you, the categories of sources from which we collected your personal information, our purposes for collecting or selling your personal information, the categories of your personal information that we have either sold or disclosed for a business purpose, and the categories of third parties with which we have shared or sold personal information;
* The right to request that we delete the personal information we have collected from you or maintain about you.
* The right to opt out of our sale(s) of your personal information. Please note that if you opt out of certain types of sales, we will be unable to provide you with the services that rely on such sales.
* The right not to receive discriminatory treatment by InsuranceRatesForLess for the exercise of the privacy rights conferred by the CCPA.

To exercise any of the above rights, please contact us using the following information and submit the required verifying information, as further described below:

* By email at compliance@insuranceratesforless.com
* Online at [Do Not Sell My Info](https://auto.insuranceratesforless.com/do-not-sell-my-info.html)

**Verification Process and Required Information.** We might need to request information from you to verify your identity or understand the scope of your request, although you will not be required to create an account with us to submit a request or have it fulfilled. We might require you to provide, at a minimum your first and last name, email address, street address, city, zip code, and telephone number.

**Authorized Agent.** You may designate an authorized agent to make a CCPA request on your behalf by providing them with written permission to submit a request. If you designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf, we will require the agent to submit proof of your written authorization.

**Minors under 16 Years of Age.** We do not sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age.

**Contact Information**

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us by e-mail at compliance@insuranceratesforless.com

All Rights Reserved 2011-2024 [InsuranceRatesForLess](https://auto.insuranceratesforless.com/)
